Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching
Oh! What's this?
Did you see that? Gentlemen.
I don't know.
Yay!
Matsuda-san's live feed started at midnight. Yay!
I wonder if he's coming.
Today is the first time we're going to stream Matsuda-san live at midnight.
I'd like to keep this kind of "make your own radio" atmosphere.
I'd like to make it a handmade radio show.
I hope we can make it a handmade radio show.
Please enjoy the show with your eyes as well.
Everyone's calling me a yahoo!
I hope you'll listen to the show in a relaxed atmosphere.
I hope you can relax and listen to the show.
We'll be doing the show until midnight.
We'll be playing till midnight, so please come on in at midnight.
So, first of all...
First of all, I'd like to introduce the lineup for today's event.
First of all, I'd like to introduce the items we'll be serving today.
This is the first one.
Yes, and then
100 things I want to ask Mr. Matsuda.
I'm sure you've already collected a lot of letters from people using the hashtag "Matsuda-san at Midnight"...
I'd like to try to answer 100 of them.
I'm sure you're nervous about this live radio show.
The mystery of the banana is still a mystery.
You got it all right, didn't you?
Thank you very much.
Next, we have a pen name... "Borstic Curry.
Since you're wearing those clothes and glasses...
I'd be very happy if you could listen to it in the broadcast.
I'd be really happy if you could sing even a little bit of the song!
I'd be really, really happy if you could dance for me
I'd be really, really happy!
I see.
I wonder how many people know about this dress.
Hey, Mr. Matsuda, it's the middle of the night.
I've done a private video for it in the past, and that's when this "Mr. Matsuda at Midnight" was born.
I was asked to sing this song "Kadeide na daetta" at that time, and I had no choice but to sing it if I was asked to do so much.
I wonder if I can remember how to dance.
I'll try. Let me see the lyrics.
I'll take a look at the lyrics.
It's embarrassing to sing like this.
But it's embarrassing to be seen like this.
I can't sleep, I can't sleep, I can't sleep, I can't sleep anymore, I want to scream, I want to scream, I want to scream, I want to scream
I've been waiting for this jingle, I can't ask for this feeling, I can't ask for this emotion
When I wake up from the dream, it's all gone tonight all night till morning
I don't I'm not like you
I don't want to wake up from this dream all night till morning
How's everybody doing? I'm happy.
They say I'm cute. Well, I'm feeling a little more relaxed now.
I'm looking for any requests or questions you may have, even during the live broadcast, so please use the hashtag
Please tweet us with the hashtag "Midnight Live Matsuda-san" and we'll get back to you.
Next
Next!
Here it is!
This is a one phrase whispering by Matsuda Onoka, and I'm not asking for any requests in advance, but I'd like to ask you to whisper something to me, Matsuda Onoka, during this live broadcast time.
Well, this is really one phrase, but it doesn't have to be just one word.
It doesn't have to be a single word, but it can be anything, even a few sentences.
You see, this is something that I've already done.
I'm nervous because I'm going to come here and read it suddenly without looking it over.
I'm nervous.
But that's how I'm going to do it.
Okay, then.
What's this? Oh, that's a model.
I'll give it a shot.
Whispers.
Here we go.
Today's the day.
All night long.
We're gonna have a good time together.
Oh, my God, am I doing this?
I'm gonna do it. You guys don't have to be so sweet about it, really.
I'm just waiting for the "screw you" moment.
I'm waiting. This is embarrassing. This is a corner that will drain your spirit.
We'll be looking for one-phrase submissions like this.We will also be soliciting one-phrase phrases like this.
Yes, sir!
I hope you can tweet about it on the hashtag "Matsuda-san at Midnight".
And although it's not written here, I'd like to call our guest at around 24:00.
I'd like to call the guest at around 24:00.
I don't want to tell you who it is yet.
I'd like to keep it a secret.
Let's take a look.
You've already whispered a lot, haven't you?
I'll be waiting for you like this.
I think we can have a little free talk.
They usually broadcast a radio program called "Hinatazuka High School Broadcasting Club" on the Nippon Hoso Kyokai.
I'm usually on the air on Saturdays from 10:00 to 10:30.
I talked about some things on that time, but this time I'd like to show you a more relaxed after party kind of thing.
I'd like to make this an after-party type of show.
I think it's rare to see a radio show
You don't often get a chance to see it with your own eyes.
So I was wondering if there is something we can do to make it more enjoyable for the eyes as well.
Well, it was a while ago.
I celebrated my 24th birthday on April 27.
And at that time, well...
I received a lot of birthday presents.
I wanted to open them properly after receiving them, so I opened them, but I haven't been able to use them yet.
So I would like to take this opportunity to use them together with you all for the first time.
Okay, then.
What shall we do?
This is what Kanamura gave me.
This is Den
I got this takikomi-gohan (rice cooked with octopus)
I haven't had dinner yet, so I'm going to make octopus rice.
I'm going to make octopus rice.
This is amazing! What is it? Is it octopus? What is it?
Burdock? Carrot? Oh, wow.
Separate from the octopus.
Separate from the octopus. Kanamura gave me this.
He gave me octopus rice and other stuff, but I thought I'd make rice.
Well, I'm really free today.
I brought a rice cooker.
I think I'll leave it here for now.
I'm going to make it right now.
I've prepared the rice here.
Oh, we can cook it here?
Oh, this?
I cook rice in a pot.
I've never used a rice cooker.
So this should go in there with it.
Has everyone eaten? How's it going?
Chop-chop.
Yeah, it's gonna take a while to cook the rice, so I'm gonna go ahead and do it.
Let's do it.
You guys want to see this?
You want to see it? - Oh, after it's done.
Oh! Oh, wow!
Smells so good! Oh, great, great, great.
Oh!
It smells so good!
And now for the main part... octopus!
Oh, this is really being delivered, isn't it?
Weird.
Too weird!
Yay!
All right, all right, all right
Now, let's take this
One moment.
What? Really?
Looks like we're on trend two, folks.
What? Not a recommendation or anything?
Really? Really?
Thank you very much.
Would you be offended if I pull it out once?
It's okay, right?
I'm sure we can work something out.
Ta-da!
Wait a minute.
Should I mix it once?
A little bit of this.
The octopus is all hardened up. A little bit of octopus.
Say goodbye to each one.
They're all good friends.
It tastes so good in this state. What should I do?
What shall I do?
I don't know if you can hear me, but you can't hear me.
You see this?
If it's too wet, it'll spill.
And then...
Where do you put it? Oh, there it is.
Ah! Let's see...
It's good to cook fast, isn't it?
What? Scary, scary, wait, wait, wait, take it back.
Oh! Oh, this.
This is the one you have to press.
Early bloomers!
What? It's like my appointment time or something.
What?
It's like 12 hours away.
Wait!
I have to keep pressing this to get it to zero.
Wait, wait, wait, I want to cook it right now.
Wait! I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I really don't have time for this.I'm sorry, I really don't have time for this.
It'll be an hour or so.
Please help me with this.
Oh!
I got it, I got it, I got it.
What? I can't start cooking rice.
And I didn't get my face right the whole time. I'm sorry.
Help me.
One more time, huh? What do I do? Start cooking rice.
It doesn't say how many minutes left. Is that okay?
What? I'll leave it alone.
It's glowing.
But it doesn't say how many minutes left.
What? It's hot! It just got really hot.
One time, I'm embarrassed.
I'm so embarrassed.
Hey, but... you know that cooking session we had at Nichinai?
I think it said how many minutes left to cook.
I'm going to press the start button one more time.
If it doesn't cook, it didn't cook.
It's not good...
Help me, help me!
I'm sure there's some steam coming out of this thing.
If it's warm...
Lilin'...
That's right.
One little try.
But don't unplug it.
Can I unplug it?
I think we should get a rice cooker.
For just such an occasion.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
I don't understand.
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
Listen, you all look so kind.
Smile at me.
So sweet.
They said we've already spent 16 minutes.
That's not true. We've got a lot of work to do. What's next?
This one.
De De De De De Den Den Cha Ran. Here you go.
De De De De De De De De De De De De De De De De De De De De De De De De De De De De De
This is Uno and quite a few others.
I'm the Year of the Rabbit.
It's the year of the rabbit.
She gave me this as a present.
I don't know why I haven't been able to do it yet.
The reason why I haven't been able to do it yet is...
I had to prepare a lot of things.
Brushes, brush pens, paints, pencils, wood glue...
I didn't have any at home.
So today, they prepared some things for me, so I'm going to do it.
I wonder if I can cook octopus rice? But I'm not sure if I can do it if I ask the staff to do it.
I'm getting worried.
Oh, sure, I got it.
Interesting. - A rice cooker...
It's hard to cook rice with a rice cooker without practice.
I'm afraid I have reservations.
Terellen...
Wow, that's amazing! It's perfect.
It's like writing on a blank slate.
It's a test of taste, isn't it?
I'm so happy because I don't often buy ornaments like this for myself.
Now it's Shired's birthday opening corner!
Let's see...
I'm going to paint.
Red and...
I want to make it look like Mr. Matsuda in the middle of the night.
Rabbit
Since we're going to this trouble...
I got this from my sister.
It's not a meat bun. It's not a meat bun.
It's a rabbit.
Is this the kind of thing that doesn't need to be diluted with water?
Maybe I should do a rough sketch... but I think it's just momentum.
I was in a school where we had to choose between music and art.
I went to a school where we had to choose between music and art.
I can't read music.
I'm not good at reading.
People often say I looked like I took piano lessons.
But I didn't take piano lessons either.
The only thing I could play was the recorder.
I don't know...
I thought I didn't have much musical sense, so I started to play the guitar partly because of that.
So I started writing.
That's why I took the pictures.
I didn't shoot because I was good at it.
I had a teacher helping me.
Don't tell anyone.
Hmmm...
It's difficult, isn't it?
I wonder if the octopus rice is ready.
But I didn't see anything about the number of minutes left.
Uh, just a little more.
A little more... a little more... a little more...
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Phew.
I thought I was going to go all Matsuda Midnight on you, but...I thought it would be like Mr. Matsuda in the middle of the night.
I can play the recorder. That's right, isn't it?
There was a corner called "Makoca's Corner" where they would challenge themselves in various ways, but I think that was the story...
You know...
I'm going to sound a bit like Kramer here, but...
It was a 100-yen recorder. That's why I couldn't play it well, in my opinion.
I used to play it at the Kigaku concert when I was a student, because I could only play the recorder.
So I played the soprano recorder.
The one from "Jounetsu Tairiku" (Continent of Passion).
I was singing.
I didn't sing.
I was watching.
What do you think? Isn't she pretty cute?
Pinto.
Hey, it's cute.
And...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I was playing on "Jounetsu Tairiku" (The Continent of Passion)
But you know, all the girls were learning piano.
I was like, "Piano, piano, piano, piano.
And then I was like...
I was like, "Piano, piano, piano, piano," with a recorder in between.
I was like, "Piano, piano, piano, piano.
Well, I was just thinking...
Yeah.
So, yeah, it was...
It was embarrassing.
All the girls were learning.
When I see a model, I want to follow it.
Point, point, point...
I'll make it thicker.
I wonder if they'll fall asleep?
When I'm working quietly...
Mane-san was so nervous.
Hmmm...
Yeah, she was nervous.
She was so cute.
Mane-san.
Here's Manet-san looking nervous.
He's a broadcaster.
Mr. Manet...
He's so nervous.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, he was nervous.
He's watching us from a broadcaster's point of view.
He's watching us now.
Ears!
Wow!
Oh, but you know what?
I was going to use psyllium colors.
Nope.
Not so much color.
Well, you know... before...
I remembered that rabbit
I've been a cheering supporter
I'm a supporter of the World Table Tennis Championships.
With an announcer named Akira Fukuzawa.
We had a live broadcast.
And he said something behind the scenes...
How long have you been here? He asked me what year I am.
I told him I was a rabbit.
I told him I was a rabbit, and he said, "I'm the same as you! And he said, "I'm the same as you!
That's right.
I met someone twice my age for the first time.
Well, maybe I did, but it's not like we're talking about that kind of thing.
Oh, the rice cooker!
He said he'd cook it himself. I wonder if it'll be like that again.
I wonder if it'll work... Salt, salt, salt, salt, pepper...
Salt, salt, salt, pepper...
Thank you for watching.
What's the time?
Is there a light here? The cooking part.
It's not glowing.
Can we go?
I'm so anxious!
Wait, I don't think that's the same stamp.
Yes, that's why you were so desperate to show us this.
I was so anxious that I asked for a copy too.
First of all, there's a power supply, a power outlet, a power outlet, a power outlet, and a menu to plug in.
I put it in the opposite direction.
I put it like this.
Quick hug, three.
Ignore the dots and start cooking rice.
What's that noise?
What is it?
I think it's done.
Oh, yes.
It's supposed to be good.
Yeah, I'm getting this dot-dot-dot.
But it's okay, because the rice cooker's glowing right there.
It's not glowing?
Yeah, it's glowing.
I might not be able to cook taco rice forever.
But shouldn't it be glowing?
But it's terrain.
Do you want to press it again?
It's glowing. Start cooking rice.
Well, let's leave it, right? Let's leave it. One time.
Hmm?
I don't hear anything.
Oh...Oh, my God.
You must be hot.
Yeah, I'm good. I'm good. I'm good.
You're gonna be fine.
Okay, I think I'm done.
You look so pretty.
And here...
I'm gonna put the date on it, just to remember I did it today.
It's a rabbit with no twist.
Excuse me.
I said something about a rice cooker.
I used all my strokes.
I shouldn't have written the name in red.
Black, but if you mix it with black, it'll all be black.
It doesn't matter if you mix it with red.
Okay, here we go.
Midnight.
Today is June 10th.
June
June 10th.
Don't you put a dot after the date?
It's this way.
No.
I wonder if you focused on the face.
(inaudible)
Year of the Rabbit
I'll do my best.
It's already been the Year of the Rabbit
It's already been 6 months!
Hey...
Okay, put it here. I've got something solid, so let's just put it here.
Red carpet, like this.
What's this? What's this?
What's this?
Oh.
I see it.
It's a vertical wooden sign with words written with a pen.
I'll write "Mr. Matsuda at midnight" here.
Which one?
Pencil. Pencil is fine.
Let's write it here.
I see it.
Is the rabbit a gift for the viewers? I mean...
I wonder if we can give it to the viewers as a gift.
But, hey, my sister gave it to me.
I don't know how I'm going to get it.
Oh, it's red.
I thought it was black, but it's red.
I'll just write it in red.
Oh, man.
Yo.
Matsuda-san.
Okay, it's done!
Matsuda-san's rabbit at midnight is done.
All right.
It was a leisurely craft time. Here you go.
We're looking forward to hearing from you. You're sending them to us?
I wonder if he's still eating...
I wonder if it's still warm enough to cook rice in the outside like this...
I'm worried. I'm worried it won't cook rice.
And...
I found a tail, so I'll put it on too.
Just in case.
Oh, it's been 30 minutes already?
What am I doing now?
The time has flown by so fast!
I'm going to turn the temperature down a little bit.
Hot, hot, hot.
Usagi's tail.
It's hard to do this kind of thing.
It's difficult, isn't it?
What is this? Bond?
What?
Huh!
Open it.
Oh, it's done.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
But... but... but...
You're not fooled, are you? I don't know.
I didn't think it was supposed to be like this because there's a slit right here.
Oh, okay. I see what you're getting at.
What's this? You don't have to do anything.
Oh, no, thank you.
Ew.
Ho-ho-ho.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm gonna roll in my diaper.
What? Is the bunny's tail right?
Well, it's not like I'm making up the right answer.
Soon I'll be like this.
I'll turn around.
Okay.
There we go. Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
What's next? There's lots of stuff.
Today. Deden.
Is this the last one? Oh, there's more. This way.
Let's take this one.
Let's take this one down.
Mmm-hmm.
I think it's hanging. This way.
This is the candle that Sooka gave me.This is a candle that Suka gave me.
This one...
I heard it's called the "Bonfire Candle" in the world.
And Kage-chan gave me a candle from the same place.
So I have two candles, but I wanted to try them out today.
Chakaman.
Will it work?
With this...
I'm getting nervous.
I think I'll try this one first.
I hope it works.
Unlock it.
I'll give it a try.
Okay. - Okay.
What the hell?
I must've swallowed it.
Oh! There it is, there it is, there it is.
Huh.
What?
I can hear you.
Can you hear me?
Can you guys hear me?
The hashtag is so far to the right, I can't see it. I'm sure.
Thanks.
Can you hear me?
Maybe I'll put a little louder one on.
Once.
Many times louder.
Just once.
Get that paper out of here.
Is the air conditioning too loud?
I'll turn it off.
Let's see, I'll turn it on.
You can see it, can't you?
You want the whole place turned on like this?
Oh, great, great, great, great.
Can you hear that? Guys?
Is this going to spread out? To the side.
If I blow on it, will it spread a little?
Oh, no.
I turned it off.
It happens all the time.
You know, like when you have a bonfire and you blow on it with a fire stick.
You blow on it with a fire stick, and it spreads.
I thought it was the same principle, but it didn't work.
Here...
Instead of waiting for the whole fire to spread...
Put a little bit of it on.
It smells good, doesn't it?
Oh, wow.
Can you hear the crackling?
Yeah, we're gonna play it safe.
Let's lock it down.
Scent.
I don't know what it is.
It smells like someone else.
I've smelled something like that before.
White tea and jasmine.
And this one?
Can you hear that?
And this one...
It's a little...
It's kind of woodsy, though, isn't it? A little woodsy?
It says right here.
Oh, it's woodsmoke.
I knew it. It smells like wood.
Oh, that's good.
Okay, I'll turn it off.
It's a little dangerous, isn't it?
Okay.
Yes.
Wow, that's...
It's a soothing scent.
It's amazing.
It's like a real bonfire.
You guys keep telling me to be careful.
I'm gonna turn off the big one.
Okay, okay.
It smells so good.
Hey, it's a little ASMR-ish, right? You know what I mean? Sound.
That's it. That's it.
Okay. And...
Is that the last one? Oh, there's more.
I'd like to move on to the corner.
Well, I guess we can't just keep doing birthday stuff, right?
Let's start with
Let's go.
Let's take it easy
This way
I'll do 100 things I want to ask Mr. Matsuda.
I'll turn it on for a minute.
You got it!
What do you think is coming?
Uh, pen names.
I'm Kono-chan, the smartest member of the group who came in third place in the recent achievement test,
When you were a student, were you the type to study hard for regular tests for several weeks in advance, or were you the type to cram right before the test?
I was the type of person who studied for the test several weeks in advance or crammed in the test right before it was due.
I was the type of person who crammed in the day before the test, without doing anything at all for a week or so before the test,
Midterms and finals are divided into several days, right?
Then, after the first day of the test was over, I would cram for the test in the morning,
After the first day's reinforcement, the test usually finishes in the morning, so you go home and take a nap,The test usually finishes in the morning, so I would go home and take a nap,
I would then go home, take a nap, start studying, work until morning, take the test, go home, and go to bed.
I would go home and go to bed. That's why I crammed so much in advance.
I was cramming in advance, and it didn't stick in my head at all. That's why it's not good for
It was not good for my academic ability.
I was doing the same thing.
I don't know why. I don't get turned on until nighttime.
So.
So, I was a super last minute cramming type.
Who's sleeping in your bed?
I'm not sleeping. There's a little bird, though.
Okay, let's continue.
Pen name, Gyoza-san tonight.
Today's live YouTube broadcast will be the first time for many of you to see her.
So, here's a suggestion.
Let's do a nostalgic catchphrase. My catchphrase?
The natto one? That's all I've ever done. Well, are there really many people who have never seen it before? Well, there is at least one person. Then, let's talk to that person.
I'm 24 years old, from Kyoto, Japan, and I'm Takanoka Matsuda, a natto lover.
I won't allow it. I'm so embarrassed.
I'm so embarrassed... please hurry up and go to the next one.
Let's see... Radio name: Shinshin-san.
When and where did the word "Yahosu" come from?
I don't remember that much about Yahosu.
I don't remember that much myself.
When was it?
I wonder if it's not a period of self-restraint?
I really don't know.
It was like a "yay-ho" kind of thing.
Like, "Yay!
I think I sent it through a messaging app.
And from there...
After a few days...
And then it started to take root.
But...
It doesn't really mean anything.
Yahos...
It can be anything. So it can mean "yoo-hoo" or "bye-bye" or "bye-bye" or "bye-bye".
It can be anything.
Don't tell me you're lonely... and you're 24.
I was 18 when I started and now I'm 24.
Oh? It's a little warm.
Can I take a look?
Can I look at it?
Like, you're not supposed to open it in the middle like this.
I'll just open it up once.
Here we go.
Right here.
You're okay, right?
Oh, my God.
It erupted! The octopus! The octopus was dancing!
The octopus was dancing! Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah! That was good! But it's like a rice cooker that doesn't tell you how many minutes are left.
Okay.
I want to see the next 100!
I've been a sun worshiper since my third Hinatan Festival, but ever since I found Kono-chan, I've been hooked on her and I've been enjoying every day of my life.
I happened to meet up with a friend I haven't seen in 15 years at last year's tour! Hinatanzaka is the best!
It's been 15 years, right? But I'm surprised you noticed that after 15 years...
I'm sure it's easy to change one's mood or appearance after 15 years...
But you're on tour, right? That's so cool. I'm dreaming of something like that.
Was the air conditioner too loud?
It's automatic...
Wind nice. But the sound is the same?
Air volume
Automatic is the only way.
Quiet. It's quieter now, isn't it?
Is this okay? Let's continue...
Let's continue... YUJI KAKKO, pen name
I cried at the Rabbit, and I cried three times when I danced, and I cried when I talked about it, and I cried when I remembered it.
Back then, he cried and laughed because he was so buggered.
Yes, I was crying a lot at that time, and I'm not sure if I'm still as strong as I was then, but I was crying a lot at that time.
I cried a lot during that period.
I think people thought, "What's wrong with him?
I don't know what it was, maybe I was thinking too much, I don't know.
I don't know.
I'm glad if you laughed.
When I was crying...
When I was fighting with Lui...
I wonder why it became so loose.
Well, maybe it's the end of the holidays.
I guess it's hard not to cry when you're feeling so emotional.
It's difficult to keep from crying.
I'm looking for a stronger way to fight the cumulative battle.
Crying three times here and there, and then crying on the way home.
I wonder if I could do that if I was asked to cry in an acting role.
I don't know if I can cry.
I haven't done a good crying act yet.
I'd like to try it someday.
Everyone's so kind. They're saying it's because I'm Leah.
Summoning.
I'm sure you're right.
10Name Jyuju-san, you're a regular on "The Time" so I have a strong image of you going to bed early, but have you been up late lately?
I'd love to hear about your midnight episodes.
I've been up late at night lately, but I was up late yesterday, too.
I should have left the house around 3:00 p.m.
That's right, so you don't have to get up early.
I'm sure I'll be up late the day before.
I'm not sure what I'm doing, though.
And...
I can't move fast at all, so when I get home from work.
So when I get home from work, I find myself on the couch for two hours or so.
I don't know why, but sometimes when I get home, I just switch off and can't do anything.I don't know why, but sometimes when I get home, the switch just goes off and I can't do anything.
So, uh, is this noisy or should I turn it off once?
Why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why
Crackle!
I've accumulated quite a lot of fragrance, so yes.
One time.
I wonder what time she goes to bed. Well, but...
What time do you usually go to bed?
Usually around 2:00 or 3:00.
But when it's my "the time" I try to go to bed before it's too late.
Yes, yes, yes.
Pen name: Mr. Mu in the middle of the night
It's June in the year 2023. Have you ever had a situation where you were able to show your power as a woman of the year?
Oh, 2023, the power of the New Year's maidens...
But there was a real event today for a game app called Hina Koi.
I wanted to wear a yukata there.
So I bought a complete set of yukata from a shopping site.
And I brought it to the event without opening it once.
And when I opened it...
When I opened it, I found that there were no strings on the inside of the yukata.
But there were no strings at all.
I don't know what to call it.
I didn't bring any underwear or strings to tie the underwear inside.
I was in such a hurry that I thought I might not be able to wear the yukata in the worst case scenario.
Just today, Hina Kawada, a member of the group, was at a real event wearing an apron.
Was she making something? And the apron's strings matched perfectly with the strings that fasten the apron.
So I used those strings as a substitute for the apron strings.
And then there's this obi.
A yukata obi.
And then, to get the wrinkles out of the yukata obi.
To get rid of wrinkles...
There's something like a padded sheet, right?
A moldboard
But we didn't have that, either.
I used a box that Hinano brought me as a souvenir
I got a box that Hinano brought me.
and cut it out.
And I used it there.
So thanks to all of you, I was able to wear a yukata.
I think I was really lucky.
If Hina hadn't said she wanted to wear the apron
If Hina hadn't asked me to wear the apron, I wouldn't have had any strings.
That's right, there was no fastening device.
I mean, it's not that I was so lucky.
Can you see it?
If you look through this red jersey of mine, you can see it.
I don't know.
It's coming out... great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great.
That's why I thought you were a very lucky girl.
Hina-chan, yes, I tied it with the apron string.
I was tying it with an apron string, so I could have tied it with a packing string.
It was a close call.
That's lucky for you... an episode of "Yearling Girl".
And now...
Barfberry, I made a mistake.
I read your Twitter name.
I'm sorry I read your Twitter name!
I'm sorry, I didn't read your name.
I do it sometimes on my messaging app.
I'm embarrassed to explain my cheeks.
I send a selfie with my cheeks like this.
I send selfies like this.
That's what I call cheek time.
Don't bring it here.
It's embarrassing.
Like this.
I'm doing it like this. Is that okay?
Oh, God.
Oh, no.
I read your twitter name.
I changed sheets, cooked, cleaned and washed for my family.
Great!
I've already said it.
I already said it. I said "great" before you asked.
Can you please say "great" for me? I feel like I can do my best every day.
That's great.
I think it's really great.
Um...
My guess is that you're probably a man.
Higashiyama Moto-san.
Yes, I'm sure.
He's great.
I don't know if men and women go together like that.
changing sheets? Cooking? Cleaning? Laundry?
I'm a housekeeper.
Great.
Great. Really great.
I'm sure she's happy to do this for you. For the family.
Pen name Kirikirikirimai.
Kirikirikirimai
You do a lot of online shopping. Have you made any mistakes recently?
Hmmm...
Yes. A recent shopping failure?
Oh, I don't mean that I've failed.
It might sound like I've failed, but... I bought something on a certain shopping site.
I bought something from a mail order site, and it was delivered the next day.
I bought it through that service, but it wasn't delivered until the next day, and when I looked at it on my cell phone, it said it had been delivered.
So I thought, "What's that? I wondered why it said "delivered" when I wasn't there, so I waited for about 3 days.
So I waited for about 3 days, and after 3 days I still hadn't received it, but I thought I should contact customer service.I waited for about three days and still hadn't received it, but I thought I'd call customer service.
Just when I was thinking I should call customer service, it finally showed up in the mailbox.
So I'm guessing it's probably gone to someone else's mailbox.
I'm guessing that it went to someone else's mailbox.
So I'm assuming that it was sent to someone else's mailbox.
I didn't ask for this and that, so they put it in my room.
Maybe.
Oh, the exact same thing happened today?
Surprisingly...
Is that a common occurrence?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Not yet.
How long have I been off for?
But I've been off for about a half hour now.
Let's go.
Okay.
Yes, please continue.
Pen name.
Dr. KF
Question.
Have you been in touch with the best friend you talked about on ANNecrosse lately?
If you have any episodes, please let me know.
I called him about 3 days ago or something, and he said he'd call me a few days ago, but the timing wasn't right, so I finally got around to it, and he said he'd call me back.
So, let me explain it simply, for those who don't know the story...
I was a classmate of hers in junior high and high school.
I'm from Kansai and went to school in Kyoto, but one of my classmates from Kyoto moved to Tokyo and started working here.
I was really seeing her in my spare time, but I saw her quite often.
And she's transferring to Kansai from June.
She came all the way here, but she got transferred.
She was talking about how lonely she was... and how she's already moved out.
So I thought I'd like to send her a present.
I told him I'd send him some plants, and he mysteriously gave me some too.
It turned out to be an exchange of plants.
Yes, I'm from Kyoto. I'm from Kyoto.
But people often say I don't show my lead when I use honorifics.
Maybe that's why they didn't know I'm from Kyoto.
I sent it as a housewarming gift, but in the end...
I don't think it was a gift, but you're so kind.
Next, Ko-chan, tell us about your recent episodes with your family...
Radio name Kakki, yes.
Well, my family and I recently had a videophone call.
They come to my house sometimes, but my parents live in Kyoto.
So, we all called each other on videophone.
So we made a video call together.
They were reporting things like that.
That's great. I can't wait to see him again.
I'm thankful that we can talk about anything as a family.
I have to take good care of them.
I really do.
Oh, you read this.
Is that you?
Kakino Tane.
Your pen name is Rima-chan's.
This is Chan Hoss.
If you could tell your new self one thing
What would you say?
Well, you just joined, right?
So, a word from the future you.
Wow.
As it is.
I'd say, "I'm happy now.
If I knew my future self was happy, I'd be able to do whatever I wanted.
I just joined.
I don't know if I can say anything too profound, but...
I'll tell her I'm happy.
But it's hard to do that when there's a situation like this
There's only one thing to do, right?
I just have to report what's going on.
We're broadcasting live at midnight.
What? Are you okay?
Yeah.
Like this?
Okay.
Continue.
Mr. Eh, Mr. Sanhi...
I'm an eternal Matsuda san guesser with my wife.
I'm so much in love with him that I want him to grow up to be an innocent and cheerful child like Matsuda-san
I want her to grow up to be a child who can give energy to everyone
To my daughter
I named her "Konoka".
I named her Konoka.
I hope you will say something like, "Konoka-chan, please grow up healthy and happy!
If you can say something like that, our family will be very happy.
Oh, wow!
That's great!
You and your husband are pushing me!
Konoka?
I like flowers and I'm a conoca.
But this "Konoka" is "I love flowers".
I see...
I'm sure she's asleep.
I think she's sleeping now.
Well... grow up healthy and happy.
And come see me sometime.
Mmm-hmm.
Grow up fast!
Hey.
What's up? Are you okay? It's great. People with the same name.
You come here often... but now that we have a new baby...She comes here often, but...
I'm so happy to see you.
Pen name: Yomosan.
The other day, Kyoko Saito held a solo concert at MTV and sang "Koishitemo fishe wa sora o fukyuu" (The fish that loves you flies in the sky)
I was so happy that the first term students chose the second term song to sing.
Well, I couldn't go to this MTV show because of my work.
I couldn't go to MTV because of work.
I couldn't go to MTV for work, but I was so happy to see a glimpse of the video of "Fish in Love".
I think it fits Kyoko's voice very well.
I got this letter quite a while ago, and I thought I'd like to write a song about it.
I have a guitar, which you can see here... or maybe it's been hidden for a while.
How do you play?
Tadasu?
A little bit.
It's "0H". Oh, I'd love to see this with you.
Can I take this out? If it's Takeda...
It won't open or anything, right? If I unplug it...
Oh, no.
I'm not going to play for a while.
That's great, guys. It's Takeru.
Hold on a sec.
Can I watch with you?
Here we go.
Ready?
Oooooh!
Oh, my gosh.
That's great, guys.
That's great!
I got it!
I'm so hungry!
Oh, I'm so hungry.
I'm starving. What?
Wow!
What's this?
Oh, no.
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
I can't believe my eyes.
Wow!
Wow, it cooks really well, even though it cooks really fast!
Hey, can I...
Can I wait until you're done eating?
It's freshly cooked.
Looks delicious!
I brought rice dishes today.
Chopsticks!
Natto chopstick rest. Naccho gave us these too.
This is... Delicious!
What's this?
This is pero, isn't it?
Let's close it up once. The flavor is escaping!
I wonder if this is it...
Looks delicious.
It smells so good!
It sure does.
May I?
Bon appétit.
This octopus.
Oh!
Ah!
It's good, Kanemura!
Right, right?
Can I make a phone call?
Yuck!
The one that goes well together.
Delicious
Oh, it's so good!
Can it be connected? Let's make a phone call.
Kanemura, call Kanemura.
Kanemura.
Kanemura, where are you?
Is that Miku?
It's Miku.
I'll call her.
I hope it works.
Come on.
(phone rings)
Hello?
Oh, my God.
What were you doing?
I was watching you.
You were watching?
I was watching you. I was watching you. I've been watching you from the beginning.
Oh, my God. Thank you. I'm glad.
It's so good. I'm glad it's bamboo.
I'm glad it's bamboo. I was really nervous at first.
The rice cooker went away once.
I threw up in the rice cooker once.
I thought I'd never make it.
I was in a hurry, but I'm glad I managed to cook it.
Congratulations, it's so good, I want you to eat it. I want you to eat it for your birthday, too.
I'm so comfortable with your delivery. Really?
You sound a little sleepy.
You've already taken a bath. I've taken a bath. I'm trying to create an environment where you can sleep.
Then we're just about there. Wow, that's nice.
That's great. Thank you.
Thank you. I'm sure they're all in there like that.
Maybe they're all asleep.
That's one way to do it. Yeah.That's one way to look at it.
Yeah, because it's the middle of the night.
It's the middle of the night, so yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's the best part. Hey, thank you.
I'm glad you're watching. I've been watching.
I'm glad you're watching.
Is there anything you'd like to share with anyone who's listening?
Oh, my God, you're just throwing that out there. Throwing it out there?
I was just wondering if you had anything to say.
You can make me a request. A request?
But you said you'd play guitar.
Yes, that's right, that's right, that's right. I'm doing that, for sure.
Maybe you should ask Kanamura for a request too.
Seriously?
You did it!
For me?
For Kanemura.
I'll sing for Kanamura, too
Sorry, guys.
I'm so happy for you.
Really?
You weren't just singing for me.
Look at me without makeup.
I'm telling you the truth.
Then listen to me.
I'll sing it to Kanamura.
I'm sorry if I fall asleep singing you a lullaby.
That's okay. That's okay, too.
I'm glad.
That's part of the fun.
Yeah, that's fun too.
All right.
I'll see you later.
Thank you.
I'll be looking for your appointment.
You, too.
All right, bye.
Great. Good luck.
Okay. Thank you.
Bye-bye, little girl.
Bye-bye.
Bye-bye, Con.
I've never said "kon-chan" before.
Hey, hey, hey, let's go, okay?
Okay.
Okay, I'm out.
Oh, my God! Kin, you're up.
You've already finished your bath.
Just let it out once.
Can I have some more food?
You've got a big appetite.
Oh!
Natto's outside.
But after singing.
I think we should treat ourselves.
What do you think?
I think I'm going to pull it first.
I know I shouldn't talk with it in my mouth like this.
I know, but I said it.
Okay, bye.
I'll be back in a minute.
I got it.
It's good.
Today... as you can see...
You brought a lot of stuff.
I brought my carry-on today.
When I met Kumi-san, he asked me where I was going.
I told him, "All these are for the live broadcast.
That's what happened.
I was asked if there were any songs I wanted to sing that I wasn't a part of, so I thought, "I'd like to play something.
So I thought I'd like to play a song that I'm not a part of, and I'd like to perform it today.
So today I'm going to play this one. I'm going to play a little octopus.
I looked like a traveler, and I had my guitar on my back.
He had a guitar on his back, so he looked like a guy traveling around.
I was like...
All right, all right, all right, all right.
Okay, I'm gonna go away for a little bit.
Okay, what are we going to sing?
The 2002 group.
I don't like you this much anymore.
I'd like to sing
for short.
I think it's called "Blind Marriage".
Blind love?
I don't know if I like blind love or blind marriage.
I think blind love is cuter.
Wait a minute.
I'll start singing.
I don't know if I'll ever love you this much again... if I ever meet someone else.
I'd meet someone else I'd never love again I'd meet someone else I'd meet someone else I'd meet someone else I'd meet someone else
I'm out of class
From the caledio
I heard the intro.
I guessed the title.
But please...
I don't want you to notice
It makes it awkward for me to be around you.It's awkward to be around you.
I don't like you this much anymore
I can't see anything but you
You were born for me
Why is the sunset so sad for the first time
You were my friend
Mom laughed and said it was love
Can I borrow the dress in your closet?
I want to be with you like this forever
I want to grow up at the same speed
I don't want to be in a relationship with someone else.
I can't even think about going out with someone else.
I can tell you right now, right now...
I don't like you any more than you like me.
I don't like you.
Put the car seat down.
Let me dream
The wind feels so good
I don't like you any more
I don't like it
I don't know if I'll ever love anyone else
Even if I met someone else
Thank you very much.
I don't like you this much anymore.
Yes, Kanamura, it's also a song that I participate in
This is just for you
Once...
I'll put this in the back.
How was it? I was nervous.
Nervous.
Put this down for a second.
We were just doing this, right?
Yes, sir.
I'm glad. It's a great song.
It's a really great song.
It's a very calm song.
And...
I thought it would go well with the evening.
This song...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I wish you wouldn't go to sleep.
It's true, it was a bit like a lullaby. Thank you.
Great night, huh?
Great. Thank you.
Thank you. - Yeah, I've been practicing this song.
And, uh...
You know, there's something I skipped earlier in the birthday segment.
Let's do that.
Ta-da!
Don't you all recognize this one?
I don't know. Some of you might.
Yes, the desks are getting jammed.
This is a questionnaire that Hinakoi did, asking what I'd like to send for my birthday.
Everyone voted for natto goods in the survey, and I received it.
I haven't used it yet, so I've been thinking I'd like to use it for a special occasion.
So, since I haven't been able to use it yet...
I want to eat natto now, too.
Natto, is it outside? I'm going to check it out.
natto
There it is, right there
Wow!
I'll take one at a time.
Two at a time.
I'm home!
Natto (fermented soybeans)
Well...
They prepared two kinds... and I'll open one.
It's a little bigger than the other one.
I wonder if I can mix it up...
Let's do our own natto blend. Here.
Take natto out into a bowl and knead it well without adding anything. Knead it well until there are a lot of strings and it becomes hard to stir.
Add soy sauce in the middle.
That seems to be the style.
Let's try it.
Will it work?
Then, this...
It's amazing how much stuff you've piled up.
Excuse me.
Wow.
That's great.
You know, it's not often you get to mix things by machine.
This one.
I'll mix one more.
It's starting to look like a garbage dump.
Thank you for watching.
Here you go.
Oh, this is...
This one.
Natto (fermented soybeans)
Natto!
Yes, in my house
Natto
Natto is an intonation.
So after I came here
I said I'm Takayuki Matsuda, a natto lover.
Hmm? Huh?
Natto is correct?
That's right.
He told me it was natto.
That was the first time.And that was the first time
I learned the intonation of natto
Natto.
That's right.
It's not Kansai dialect or something? I don't know.
I'm not sure.
It's a full set.
That's great.
Ultimate mode
Extreme
Oh, I have a knob here.
I'd like to do it in ultimate mode.
Can we do it? We have to close it tightly.
Oh, it's so hard!
This hard?
What?
Is it okay?
Oh, wow.
Oh, it's mixed in.
Did I put too much in? Oh, but, uh, does it sound really gross? A little bit.
Hey, sorry if you don't like squeaky sounds.
It's hard.
Is it supposed to sound like this?
I don't know. Squeaky? What?
Pick it up. Already?
Already soy sauce time? It's a little early.
I mean, put the soy sauce in!
So fast! Faster than I thought!
I'll put this sauce in now.
Really?
Maybe I used it wrong.
I thought I assembled it properly.
But there's a hole for soy sauce.
You know, it doesn't sound good.
Maybe I didn't mesh well?
Hmmm...
It's rejected.
Oh, it's closed.
It's closed.
What?
That doesn't sound good.
You know, it's a little bit loud for my ears.
It's been... it's been open forever.
No, I don't know, maybe I'm just not using it right.
But you're supposed to close it like this.
It's all mixed up. It's all mixed up.
It's hard to tell.
I don't know, maybe it's just something I did wrong, but it sounds a little...
I'll take a look at it.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
I don't know... but it says to put it in 305 times.
I'm using it too hard.
This is a live feed. Why?
Why?
Why? This way?
But it sounds weird no matter which way I turn it.
Maybe it's the rice cooker. Maybe I'm just not very good with machines.
Wait a minute.
Let's see... But turn it this way.
Let's hold it from the knob side.
Okay, hold it from this knob side.
Okay, like this.
Oh, when closing the soy sauce door, turn the handle at least 10 times while holding the soy sauce door.
Open?
Sort of.
I don't know why.
I read it carefully.
Maybe I shouldn't have put two packets in there. I was greedy.
I was greedy.
I don't know.
I don't know. I'm going to turn it on by itself.
If it makes a sound, I must be wrong.
Oh, but it doesn't make any sound.
The pressure of the natto must be really strong.
That's why.
Can I do a little more research?
You know what?
This makes it sound like I'm doing a negative promotion.
It's like I'm doing a negative promotion.
With this.
One time.
Can I put it on taco rice? Half.
Once.
With this, right?
But I don't think there's a specific amount that's prescribed in a packet.
Let's do it again.
Now you tighten it up like this, right?
Make this mode the ultimate.
And then...
Oh, no. But it's a little lighter than before.
Is there such a thing as an accident? Is there such a thing as an accident?
Right?
Maybe it's the stickiness, maybe it's the pressure.
What? Maybe it is.
The gap from the sound of the playing is indeed.
I wonder if anyone woke up to this squeaky sound when trying to fall asleep with it?
But when I took it off, this squeaky sound doesn't come out, so maybe it's just the pressure of natto.
So, it is this one.
Well, let's just say that this is all done, shall we?
I hope you don't mind.May I?
If you don't like the sound of this...
What are you doing here at 12 o'clock?
I'm just now... it's 12 o'clock... I'm really going to eat some octopus rice and natto...
I'm going to eat some tako-rice-natto.
I'm going to eat some takoyaki rice and natto.
I'm still waiting for the 100 whispers and this...
I'm still waiting for you to whisper to me.
I'm also looking for things you want to whisper to me.
I'll call you Mr. Matsuda at midnight for now.
Okay.
I'll leave you alone at midnight.
It's a nuisance to the neighborhood, that's for sure.
I wonder why it happened.
Maybe I put too much natto in.
Bon appétit!
Yum!
Delicious!
Ah!
But it might be better if you eat it separately.
After all...
Tako-Meshi is delicious on its own, so this is a little bit.
Bon appétit!
Yum.
It's so good!
Mm-hm-hm-hm.
Oh!
It was delicious.
I'll wipe my hands.
De-den.
All right.
The desk is getting rougher and rougher.
I think I'll just leave this here for now.
All right
That's it.
Did you smell that natto? Let me get back to you on that.
I'll send it to you somehow. I'm sure it'll work.
I'm sure it'll work.
Let's see what we can do next.
It's definitely 24:00.
Maybe I should call the guests. Right here.
I don't know if they're awake, but...
I don't know.
But call him.
I said I'd call them.
I'm sure he'll be awake.
Here you go.
I wonder who it is.
I'll let you know when I get him on the line.
Let's see if it works.
I'll just take a quick glance at the water.
I can't make a phone call with a mouthful of natto.
Good.
Here we go.
Can you make it?
Who could that be?
Is he asleep?
But it's after midnight.
It could be close.
What do you think?
I think this might be the one that's really not picking up.
Excuse me, sir?
Actually, but he called.
We were talking on the phone.
I was talking on the phone.
I said I might have slept with the member today.
She might be sleeping with him.
What?
Let's wait till this thing wears off, gentlemen.
Well, maybe he's just tired.
Great.
Oh, no.
It didn't work.
Okay, well, let's just try one more time.
I'm going to go change my clothes.
In the meantime...
Wake up, everybody.
I don't think you know who she is.
I don't think you know who she is, but please pray for her to wake up.
This is a live feed.
I said I'd call you.
I said I'd call you, but apparently I can't get a signal right now.
Okay, everybody.
Well, if you'll excuse me, I'm gonna get changed.
I'm gonna get dressed now, and I'll be gone.
Don't disappear. Get dressed.
I'll go change. Bye.
See you later.
I wonder why he's sleeping.
I wonder if she's sleeping.
I wonder if she's sleeping. Okay.
Is he sleeping?
Is she sleeping? Good.
Is she asleep?
Is she sleeping?
Is she sleeping? Good.Is he sleeping? Okay.
Is he sleeping? Okay.
Is he sleeping?
Is she sleeping?
Is she sleeping? Good.
That's it.
The end.
Daddy-daddy-daddy-daddy-daddy-daddy-daddy-daddy-daddy-daddy-daddy-daddy-daddy.
papa-papa-mapa-mapa-mapa-mapa-mapa-mapa-mapa.
888Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa
888PaPaPaN
papa-papa-papa
I'm home.
Hey, guys.
Aren't you all asleep?
You didn't say a word, did you?
Are you asleep?
Did they wake up? I'll make one more call.
Can I call you later? I'll call her later. She might be taking a bath or something right now.
I didn't give a definite time.
I'm done getting dressed.
Yes, I'm done changing. I'll do it here.
Please take care of it.
Do you know what these pajamas are?
Yes.
They are pajamas of Mr. O'Dooley's goods. It's the middle of the night, so I thought I'd change into pajamas.
I thought I would change into pajamas too. I thought I'd go from my midnight Matsuda-san mode to a little bit more
I was sleeping.
That's true.
But it sure feels like a school trip, doesn't it?
But I've heard that school trips are usually in uniform, but on a school trip, you can suddenly see them in their casual clothes.
I've heard that people get excited when they suddenly see some civilian clothes on a school trip.
I went to a school that didn't have uniforms... so I've always wanted to wear one.
The last uniform I had was in kindergarten.
Good night, Miffy.
Wake up, Miffy!
Hey.
It's Saturday, and there's a radio show... and Mr. O'Dolly's radio show.
I don't know.
I wonder how Mr. Oddie's radio is going to be.
I'd like to whisper a phrase or two.
Heh.
I'll open it once.
I'm getting nervous.
Here we go.
Ten names.
Mr. Ponsa in uniform.
Duce.
Thank you very much.
Did you hear that?
Yes, ma'am.
I'm glad to see you're still a little bit gentle.
Toothless, ladies and gentlemen.
And now...
Pen name: Mr. Soh.
I'm a little embarrassed.
I'm embarrassed to say...
I'll tell you.
I'd be happy if you could just look at me.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm embarrassed because I don't get to choose anymore.
This is a dream. This is a dream.
I, yes, I'll do my best
I'll do my best
Pen name Shigeru
whoop whoop!
Don't laugh at me.
I'm laughing.
I'm laughing, I picked this one myself.
Come a little closer.
Twinkle, twinkle, twinkle.
That's a bunny.
This is...
That's the one you're talking about in this Raj.
He's smiling.
I'm so embarrassed.
I'm being told not to glare at him.
You know what?
When the words come out of your mouth...
I thought if my face was too hard...
I don't think I can kiss you.
You know...
This is a mental breakdown.
I wish the sun would do this.I wish the sun would do it.
No laughing, really. Outside. When they laugh there, you know.
Pen name, Chelle.
Bye-bye then, you're in my way
This is a Nisei song, isn't it?
I'm not sure if you want to call it the part of my lines in the recent
I'd like to say the part of the line
It's the words before the chorus of "You are in my way.
It's true, my heart
My heart is being scraped off right now, even though it's already scraped off.
I can't even use this... and my heart's been whittled down... but I'm trying my best to whisper it.
I'll try my best, but I'm not very good at it.
My name is Mr. Nature.
This is...
This is live delivery.
You can't always see the best of everything.
You can't always see the good stuff.
You see?
This is the instability
That's what live delivery is all about.
Yes, sir.
That's right.
Ladies and gentlemen...
This is embarrassing.
You can all whisper along with me.
Right?
You want to join us?
You want to?
You know, I'm getting a little tired.
I mean...
I don't know how many of these I'm gonna read.
Will I make it?
I don't know if I'm mentally prepared for this.
All right.
Whew.
Yeah.
Pen name Macha-san
ps.
My mood is now
I'm not in a "pyo-su" mood.
Right?
I know it sounds like "what the heck is a "PYOUS"?
I often jokingly call the piece "byos".
I've been doing a hell of a live delivery.
Matsuda Ono's lyrics are outrageous!
I've been allowed to live-deliver it.
I'm surprised that 31,000 people are watching this situation
I'm amazed!
Thank you very much.
There are some "let's run together" type people here.
Oh, no.
Yes. Do you have any?
Yes, I do.
That's great.
We're doing a live broadcast right now.
We're doing it while we're recruiting.
Mane-san is doing the writing.
Tonight is gyoza.
I love natto.
I love you.
I love you more.
I'm like... am I okay like this? Right now...
I'm a mix of all kinds of Matsuda right here, right now.
No way! Outrageous! Outrageous!
Yes, yes, ha!
Pen name: Vinegared rice with a hundred cups
Eh~ Monet-chan, you know what will happen if you make this girl angry, don't you?
You know that, don't you?
LOL!
Yeah, yeah, but you know what?
I wonder if everyone is awake and listening to this distribution.
I wonder if they're already open and falling asleep.
Well, it's past midnight.
Looks like the last one.
Pseudonym: Ryukichi
Wake up! Guest
It's true, wake up!
That's where it all started to go wrong.
That's a lie, though.
Phone call? You know, I'm sure some of you are looking forward to that call.
I'm sure some of you are looking forward to the call.
Let me make one more call.
Let's try again.
You're the one who wants to make it a regular thing every week.
No, no, no.
You can't do this every week.
Okay.
Okay, bye.
Can we do it? One more.
One more.
I'll try again.
Okay. - Okay.
Okay, then.
One.
Two.
Three.
Ooh!
What?What?
Hello?
Were you asleep?
I'm sorry.
I'm totally fine.
I wasn't.
I really wasn't.
Really?
It was bath time.
Are you okay?
I don't know...
The octopus rice looks delicious.
I was looking for the original recipe for takikomi gohan.
I was looking for it and scooping it out.
Then I melted it.
Are they connected? Of course it's connected.
I was in a hurry when I made the first call.
I was in a hurry.
You said she might be asleep when you saw her today.
Yes, I did.
I thought you were joking.
And once I called him, he didn't answer, so I thought maybe he really fell asleep.
Well, trouble is bound to happen, isn't it?
This is a live broadcast, right?
But I was afraid he wouldn't call again.
I'm glad you could make it.
Thank you.
Good evening.
I'm Kumi Sasaki from Hyugaizaka 46.
Captain!
Captain... after all...
I have something to say today.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
Is it okay to say such a thing here in the middle of the night, Mr. Matsuda?
Yes, go ahead and say it.
I have an announcement.
Tuesday, June 13th.
Yes.
We'll be doing a live broadcast on the Minato-zaka channel.
Oh, wow!
Crackle, crackle, crackle!
Is it in three days already?
Yeah.
It's already the 11th.
Yeah, two days.
Two days.
What?
Three days.
What are you doing? I don't know.
Um...
Is it okay if I tell you?
It's been a while.
Oh, can I say something?
Can I say it?
It's been a while.
I'm thinking of having a dumpling party.
Sounds great.
How's it going?
It's like... when you made your debut.
Debut?
Yes, it was our first anniversary, but we're thinking of reviving it.
Nice dumplings! Come here, you too!
Are you sure? You too, Ms. Matsuda? Please come, Matsuda-san.
I'll come.
Gyoza party.
I'll prepare natto, too.
Natto?
Natto gyoza?
That's good.
Yes, so the machine is back with a vengeance.
I'm so embarrassed.
It was really difficult.
It was amazing.
You know, maybe it's the performance of the microphone.
It was so squeaky.
Embarrassing.
Well, you know, it's a live broadcast.
That's the beauty of live delivery, too. You're right. Thank you, Komisato. Your comment cheered me up.
Oh, yeah? I'm glad. I'm really looking forward to the gyoza party.
I'm really glad. I'm sorry, I didn't sleep. No, not at all. It was fun.
I didn't sleep. I didn't sleep. I didn't sleep at all.
Well, I made a lot of food.
I'm sorry for disturbing you.
Thank you very much.
June 13th.
October... 13 June...
I thought it might be radio waves.
Why are you doing October?
I thought it couldn't be.
It can't be that far ahead, can it?
June 13th.
I'm thinking of doing it.
Yes, I understand.
Then I'm looking forward to working with you too.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Good luck after this.I'll do my best and continue to do so after this.
I'll do my best.
See you soon.
Yes, thank you very much.
Bye.
Okay.
Good night, Pi-chan.
Good night.
See you in your dreams.
Bye.
Seyla.
Oh, did I say something?
I think I hung up. I might have said something.
I'm sorry, Kumi. Kumi.
I thought we were done with "bye." Then I might have said something.
I don't know why I said October. I think I'm getting a little screwed up.
Asshole!
I took off my glasses.
I mean...
I mean, I mean...
I want to answer 100.
I don't know how many I've sent you.
Not at all.
Mr. Mane had a bitter look on his face.
Oh! This is amazing.
With illustrations.
Pen name Yume Neko-san
I'm going to start working next year, and I'm not sure if I'll be able to handle it.
Well, I'll hide it a little, but your illustrations are amazing.
I see, but you're going to start working next year.
I've skipped the stage of being a member of society in general...
I suddenly joined Hiragana Zelkova and started my career as an idol.
I don't have any experience as a new employee, so I can't give you any specific advice... but in the sense of challenging something new...
I guess that's exactly what it means.
Like Matsuda-san's live delivery at midnight this time... but I think it's about taking on new challenges.
But most of all...
I think the most important thing is to have fun.
I think I've made up my mind to have fun first and foremost.
I'm sure there will be a lot of anxiety and nervousness.
I may be anxious and nervous about everything, but...
But if I can look at my nervousness from a bird's eye view...
If I can look at it from a bird's eye view...
I sometimes feel like I can relax a little bit.
I can see that I'm nervous, or that I'm nervous, and it helps me to relax.
I can relax a little bit.
So, you know, maybe you should tell someone about it, or share it with someone else.
I think it's also good to share it with others.
But I'd still like you to teach me how to do it, too.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Pseudonym Saikorokke
Good evening, Ms. Matsuda-Kono!
I don't usually listen to the radio.
This is my first post.
I would be happy if this is a good opportunity for me to learn about the appeal of radio.
I have a question for you.
To you, Kono Matsuda.
what is the appeal of radio to you? I'm looking forward to hearing from you!
The appeal of radio...
I wonder what it is.
But...
Well, for me...
I started out working with Audrey-san and Hina-ai.
I started working with Audrey and Hina-ai, and they're all radio stars.
And then there was a special week where they invited guests from all over the world.
During the Hiragana Break era, some of our members were invited to the show.
I genuinely enjoyed listening to them.
I was genuinely enjoying listening to them, so I started listening to them more often.
I felt like I could get a sense of the inside of a person that was different from the side I usually work with when I listen to the radio.
That was amazing.
I mean, even people who seem so perfect, when you know that behind the scenes they are thinking and thinking like this, you can do your best.
I like that.
Also, I like the fact that it doesn't matter where I am.
But with radio, you can listen to it while doing whatever you want.
You can listen to it while doing whatever you want, even when you're taking a walk, as long as your ears are open.
You know, as long as your ears are open, you can listen to it.
I think it's really nice that you don't have to choose where you are.
I think that's really great.
If you talk at this pace, you might not be able to say a hundred things.
I might not be able to say a hundred things.
Yes.
I'm in a long-distance relationship... and I've been listening to the song "Before I Know It, I've Been Loved" by Hinatazaka 46 over and over again because it really resonates with me.
I'd like you to tell me which song you like best.
But I'll have to think of songs by all the members of Hyuga, because there are too many unit songs...
But...
Doremi? I like "Do Re Mi Solo Rashido" the best. It's very Hinatazaka.
I think Doremi is the song for Hyuuga-saka.
And I remember this period being a lot of fun, especially during the summer.
Maybe it was because it was summer.
I really like "Doremi" because I think it was a really fun period.
Doremi is my favorite.
I'm a winner for taking a bath.
I don't know how long we've been doing this.
Two hours?
Sure, 10:30.
Two hours.
Well, I got a little cold one time.
I often find myself forgetting to turn on the hot water switch a few dozen seconds after starting the shower.I often find myself forgetting to turn on the hot water switch a few dozen seconds after starting the shower.
What? A few dozen seconds after you start the shower, you turn on the hot water switch?
I didn't know there was such a thing as a switch to turn on the shower to hot water.
I've noticed that you often make mistakes, Mr. Matsuda. Mistakes.
But in this case, she forgot to turn on the hot water line, and the alarm went off.
Oh, yes...
I'm often asked to put a line in the bathtub, not a lid.
I think I have to do it right, but I have to tighten it like this, you know?
There's this line, you know, not the one you have to physically tighten.
If you press down on it, this line will be broken.
You think you're pushing it, but unexpectedly it's...
Sometimes I think I'm pushing it, but I'm not and it's floating.
That's why I have to look at it properly.
Oh, so you're talking about the rapid freezing.
Yes, yes, yes, there are many types of baths.
Pen name Ishijiro-san
I have a question for you.
When I was a child, for some reason I longed to be a cabinet secretary, but I never had one.
Did you have a dream job when you were a child?
Wow, that's the first time in my life I've ever run.
When I was in kindergarten, I wanted to be a cookie chef.
Not a cake baker, but some kind of cookie chef.
When I was in middle school...
In middle school, yeah.
But most of all, what did he say?
A pharmacist? I always wanted to be a pharmacist.
I wanted a stable job.
In the future...
I thought that even if something happens, being a pharmacist would give me a sense of stability... a job that would never go out of demand.
Yes, yes, yes.
I wanted to be a cookie chef.
But then I realized I was an idol. So I guess there's a lot of different paths to take.
Why cookies? Because they were delicious? Yes. Radio name Ripkuri.
Mr. Reem of Lipkuri, this is Chan. In your job, you meet a lot of people, how do you keep yourself in the spotlight?
I'm the type of person who gets shy if I don't see someone for a few days, even if I know them, so I'd like to hear your tips.
Me too. I guess I'm more the shy type.
I'm not sure if I'm getting along.
I don't know if I've said this before, but I'm still good at first meetings.
It's nice to meet you, so we don't know anything about each other, so we can talk about anything.
What are your hobbies? The second or third time is the hardest for me.
I think it's difficult to talk about anything after the first time.
After that, I often don't know what to say.
I think that if you are interested in the person you are talking to, you will probably have a good conversation with him or her.
That's why.
I guess there are a lot of shy people.
I'm shy even among the members.
Yes, I do.
That's great. That's exactly why I want to know too.
Well, I think it's best to talk to people when you want to talk to them.
You don't have to force yourself to open up, do you?
You can just be yourself and say, "There's nothing to talk about.
I think it's okay to just be yourself and say, "There's nothing to talk about. Then you can say, "I was thinking that too," and get to know each other.
Maybe it's okay to just be yourself. You don't have to force yourself to talk.
I'm sure you don't have to try to talk about it.
Okay, let's move on to Ms. Tsukasa, pen name. Konochan, yay!
I know you have been interested in ballet, taiko, tap dancing, light music, and many other things since before you joined us.
Is there anything that you would like to learn or experience that you have been interested in recently?
I wonder what it is.
I really wanted to learn table tennis at the World Table Tennis Championships.
I didn't have that deep knowledge, but I learned a lot of things from you.
I learned a lot of things while watching the live broadcast.
I wanted to learn the technical aspects of the game, too, and I felt like I could do it when I saw all those great people.
I had the illusion that I could do it too.
You look so sleepy.
Maybe it's because I ate dinner. I'm getting sleepy.
But I'm sure there are people who are listening to me while I'm like this, so...
I'm really interested in table tennis.
I'm really interested in ping-pong.
I want to play again.
Pen name: Kazunosuke
I've been planning a trip to Kyoto for the past three nights now that the world has finally become a place where people can easily go on vacation.
Let me ask Mr. Matsuda, a Kyoto native, for his advice!
Which business card do you want people to see the most in Kyoto?
The most?
The one I'm most impressed with is...
Sanjusangendo.
I don't know how to say it...
I think it's generally known as Kiyomizu-dera or Kinkaku-dera.
I think it's like Kiyomizu-dera or Kinkaku-dera or something like that.
I can't take a picture of it.
You can't take pictures of the inside of Sanjusangendo.
So it's a place that you can only experience by going there.
That's why I think it's a place of interest that can only be experienced by going there.
33Motomichi Yes, there are many statues of Buddha.
There are many statues of Buddha.
It's said that there is a person with the same face as you among them, so it's like looking for someone who looks like you.
I want you to look at it.
Yes, there are so many statues, it's really overwhelming, isn't it?
Yes, you can say that.
The last one?
Yeah...
Pen name Nametake46
What did you notice when you chose your own letter this time?
I also looked through all the certificates.
It's hard just to look through all of them, and it was even harder to choose carefully.
And it seemed even more difficult to carefully select from them.
It's amazing that the staff does this every week.
I also chose the ones I wanted to answer, but everyone's enthusiasm was so great that I was really lost.
So, I really had a hard time deciding.
And it's true that it's really hard to choose carefully from this list.
It's really difficult to choose from among all of them, because we had a certain period of time to recruit, and there were people who submitted their answers over a number of days.It's difficult, because we had a certain period of time to accept submissions, so we had people submitting submissions over a period of several days.
I was very happy to see people who drafted and submitted 20 or so submissions at once.
It's amazing to see how many people are doing this every week, and it's also interesting to see what other people are writing.
I think it must have been interesting from your point of view as well.
Thank you for watching my work as always. I can certainly count at least one entry.
I'm including whispers.
I'll make it 100. Let's go.
One... two... three... four...
Two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, fourteen.
Five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20.
21 22 23 24 25 26 27 28 29 30
Thirty-one. Thirty-two. Thirty-three. Thirty-four. Thirty-five.
It was Sam. It was Mr. Sam.
I didn't add up to 36 at all. It's a lot harder than I thought it would be, but it's amazing how seriously you take each one.
I just wanted to answer.
I just wanted to answer each one seriously.
A hundred.
I'm getting sleepy.
What? A member told me you got a message during the whispering.
What? That? Eight bowls of sushi rice?
Two?
Two? The members said there was something.
You're awake.
That's kind of the point, isn't it?
What? No way. From a member?
Wait a minute.
What? A whisper?
Whispers? Do you guys know what that is?
What? Which one?
Wait a minute.
Hmm.
Hmm? What? Nature?
Marie? Oh!
We're Nature, Natures, right? We're like the Nature Sisters.
What? This is Marie? No way!
Nature is Marie, and I'm a sooty weed.
It's Kin-chan.
Thank you.
And I hope you're still awake.
Marie, are you awake?
Hey, one time.
Oh, but instead of tweeting, you know, like, "Hey, Mr. Moneymane sent me...
Marie, I'm so glad you asked.
Marie, I'm so glad you asked. My sister?
I knew it when you wrote "that guy".
That's right. Everyone calls her that.
It's okay that you call me that.
Hey, Kin-chan...
Yes, I thought "sooty weed" once, didn't I?
That's right, that's right, that's right
Oh, really?
I might be awake!
I'll make one more call.
Oh, Kumi's sending me a stamp saying "Fight!
Hmmm...
I found it.
Can you make it?
Thanks for your hard work.
Wow! Really?
Good job! Really.
No, not at all.
I'm just surprised. Good job.
Good work! I'm surprised you're still awake at this hour.
Oh, well, to be honest, uh, uh...
I was going to sleep with my eyes closed for a bit. I was going to listen with my eyes closed.
I know, but...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But then I realized that I was looking at it so much!
Oh, I'm so glad.
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much!
I'm so glad.
Hey, hey, what was it, like the Nature Sisters? Nature Sisters?
Yes, it was, wasn't it? Like the Nature's Sisters.
I'm glad Marie is a bit fuzzy on the subject. Yes, I remember that the Nature Sisters were too fashionable, so we ended up being vague about it.
I remember that it ended up being vague. Nature is fine, then. Nature is indeed good, isn't it? I'm glad. It's casual. Are you playing Ammi Ho, genius?
What is it? Ammi Ho genius?
But there's something on the radio... well, it's Shikonoka's radio... but I can't sleep.
I can't sleep. It's fine, but... You're sleeping.
That's right. That's true.
She wants me to listen to her, but she also wants me to go to bed.
Really? Well, if I said that, everyone would be asleep.
Yes, everyone is waiting for you. They are asleep.
I'm sure they'll wake up. I'll definitely stay awake.
Thank you. You're so kind.
That's great. That's great. Even more amazing, really. It took me about 2 hours to do it.
Yes, more than 2 hours. I noticed.
That's great.
I'm going to have a good night's sleep.
After all.
I was awakened when Suiman was there and he told me that it was one of the members of the group.
Really?
Thank you so much.
I'm glad. Thank you very much. I was humble.
I was humble. Humble. Oh yeah, me too, I wanted to bet on it if I had to.
Yay! I'm so happy. Thank you, Marie.
Thank you. Love.
Sleep well. Yeah. You too, Marie.Sleep well. Yeah. You too, Marie.
Thank you very much. Bye.
Okay.
Thank you. You're so sweet.
What a nice junior.
What? Is this from when you were swabbing? First century?
Who is it?
Pen name, Mr. I want to eat yakiniku.
I want you to whisper to her.
What's the word?
Nibu-chan is cute!
Well, I'm cuter than you.
Good luck with your late-night delivery!
What? You mean Nibu-chan?
Nibu-chan!
Oh, yeah! Wait!
Yes!
This pen name just hit me!
I really wanted to eat yakiniku.
So I called Nibu-chan.
Yes, but Nibu-chan had plans to go out for dinner that day, so I asked her out on the same day.
Right, and she said she wanted to eat yakiniku!
Wow, that's so sweet of you!
It's funny how Nibu-chan says I'm cute.
Thank you. Are you coming too, Nibu?
Put the rice cooker away.
This? He gestured to everything.
I know...
I'd like to clean up a bit.
It's like I'm in a dream.
Well...
But... the angle of view on this feed is surprisingly beautiful.
How about this?
50 more to go!
Awww!
Well then...
Well, I'm sleepy myself, but...
I'm sure you're all getting sleepy too.
You know...
I can't believe that 31,000 people have viewed the site even at this hour.
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
I'm pretty touched that you're watching me, and I'm not sure if it's okay that you're watching me.
I'd like to say thank you at the end, so...
Can I play it for you?
This is my favorite song.
Well...
Yes, Takahashi Mikuji requested this song Sankisei
Yes, yes, yes
He said he'd like to hear this song if it's hard to play
I like it too, and I think a lot of people like it
One time
Okay, let's go
Here we go.
All of you.
Thank you.
Here we go.
One moment.
Now please listen. If silence is love.
Thank you for watching.
I was wondering if the first cicada to start crying is the last one to stop.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
You asked me out of the blue.
I don't know what you meant by that.
I'm sure it didn't mean anything.
You were afraid to be silent.
What's important to you.
It's different for everyone.
I thought it was the same for everyone.
Immaturity, youth...
It's a pain in the ass, isn't it?
I've just realized that silence...
If it's love between us, I won't force you to let go.
Now I'm just looking out at the ocean
I'll wait till the sun goes down
Our clumsy goodbye
I can't put it into words
Until it's all dark
I just want to hold her by the shoulders and stay like this.
I have to say something. I have to carry on.
Maybe that's what you're thinking.
It's heartbreaking.
I just opened a Coke soda.
You're mumbling something.
Why don't we just tell each other the truth?
You know, pride and stubbornness...
It's just a distraction for the two of you.
So, what are you gonna do? Memories.
With memories.
I'd rather just sit here
I'd rather listen to the sound of the waves.
It's a calming way to say goodbye
Like I can't hold the tenderness in my heart
I slowly close my eyelids
When the first star is shining
I wonder if there will be no one by my side
When all the sounds of the world are gone and silence reigns
I wonder if I won't be able to feel joy or sadness
If that's the case, be brave
I'll look you in the eye and talk to you
Even if it's goodbye
If silence is our love, I won't force you to let goIf silence is our love, I won't force you to let go
Now we'll just watch the sea and wait till the sun goes down
Our clumsy goodbye
I can't put it into words
Until it's all dark
I'll hold your shoulder
I just want to stay like this.
Thank you very much.
I lost my breath in the middle of the song. How was it, ladies and gentlemen?
Thank you.
I was so close at the beginning.
Well, they said we have two minutes. What? Hodley's?
What is it, Mr. Hodgley?
Oh, I see. I see. Thank you very much. Surely after this. It's almost over, guys. Thank you very much.
I know that I was quite nervous and had a lot going on for the first time, but it was really a lot of fun all in all.
I think we all had a lot of fun, and I would be very happy if we could do it again.
Thank you very much.
I hope to see you all again.
See you again in my dreams.
Bye-bye, and thank you very much. To everyone who really listened to the end.
See you soon!
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching